You look cute in bubbles.
거품 속에서 보니깐 귀엽다
You're just all liquored up.
아니, 너무 취한 거야
Hey, it's me. I'm coming in.
나야, 들어간다
I've had a very long, hard day.
오늘 너무 힘들었어
-You're home early.
-Yeah, my date threw up.
- 일찍 왔네?
- 데이트상대가 토하는 바람에
치킨 사올 건데 너도 먹을래?
Want some chicken?
아냐, 치킨은 됐어
그럼, 바이바이
No, thanks. No chicken.
Bye-bye.
You sure?
Some extra-crispy, dirty rice?
진짜야? 엑스트라 크리스피,
더티라이스, 콩은?
안 먹는다고 했잖아!
당장 나가라고!
For the last time, no!
Get out, Joey!
All right.
알았어
괜찮아? 문간에 죽치고 서서
치킨 먹을 거냐고 계속 묻잖아
Are you okay?
He wouldn't leave.
He kept asking me if I wanted chicken.
Chicken?
치킨?
I could eat some chicken.
난 먹을 수 있는데
조이!
난 치킨 세 조각이랑
양배추샐러드, 콩, 콜라...
Could I get a three-piece,
some coleslaw, some beans and a Coke?
Diet Coke.
다이어트콜라
The One With All the Kissing
- 얘들아
- 왔니, 피비?
-Morning, Phoebe.
-I have to tell you this story.
내 얘기 좀 들어봐
여기 오는데 택시기사가...
I was coming over
and this cabdriver
이름은 앵거스?
Was his name Angus?
What?
뭐?
런던에서 만났던 택시기사야
He was a cabdriver
we had in London.
하하하...
All right. Anyway
어쨌든...
What was that pub he took us to?
그 사람이 데려간
술집이 뭐였지?
The Wheat Sheaf!
- '휘트 쉬프'
- 맞아, 그 맥주는...
And they had that beer....
Boddington's!
- 보딩턴
- 맞아, 보딩턴
Phoebe was going to tell a story.
피비 얘기도 들어보자
그래, 정말 웃기는
모자를 썼더라
So he had a really funny hat.
I don't want to talk about it.
얘기하기 싫어
-Hey.
-Hey, Ross!
- 나 왔어
- 안녕, 로스?
Boddington's!
보딩턴!
Oh, man!
그 맥주 참 좋더라
I'd walk back to London for another
frosty one of those bad boys.
녀석들 때문에 걸어서라도
런던에 가고픈 심정이야
They have them at the
British pub by the Trade Center.
무역센터의 영국 술집에서
팔 거야
Later!
나중에 봐
Shouldn't Rachel be back?
레이첼이 올 때가 됐잖아?
Her plane got delayed.
비행기 출발이 연기됐나 봐
그래도 도착할 시간 됐는데
But she should be here by now.
통화했구나
화난 것 같진 않고?
So you talked to her?
Did she sound mad?
No. But she likes me.
아니, 날 좋아하잖아
You abandoned her
on a plane to Greece.
레이첼을 비행기에
버려둔 건 오빠야
난 레이첼을 버린 게 아냐
I did not "abandon" Rachel. Okay?
에밀리가 공항에 나타났다고
Emily showed up at the airport.
I had to go after her.
I did what I had to do.
쫓아갈 수밖에 없었어
난 할 일을 했을 뿐이야
She's my wife.
Rachel is my wife.
레이첼은 내 부인이라고
알아? 에밀리!
Emily!
Emily is my wife.
에밀리는 내 부인이야
Man, what is that?
방금 그게 뭐였지?
You haven't heard from Emily?
에밀리 소식은 못 들었어?
그래, 공항에서 놓친 뒤로
Not since I lost her at the airport.
I can't believe she can outrun you.
널 따돌리다니 대단하군
엄청 빨랐다고! 알겠어?
Hey! She's fast, okay?
You think you can beat me?
Let's go! Outside!
너도 날 이길 것 같냐?
그럼 밖으로 나가자!
-I'm sorry. I'm just a little
-Slow?
미안하다, 내가 조금...
- 느려?
- 너도 해볼래?
Oh, you want some?!
Okay, get the shoes on! Let's go, man!
어서 신발 신고 나가자
It's cool, okay?
진정해
You're the fastest!
오빠가 제일 빨라
-Hi!
-Oh, my God, Rachel!
- 얘들아!
- 레이첼
레이첼, 정말 미안해
뭐라고 할말이 없다
Rach, I am so sorry.
I am so, so sorry.
괜찮아, 넌 할 일을
했을 뿐이야
Come on.
You just did what you had to do.
안녕, 피비?
그래? 화 안 났어?
끔찍했을 텐데
That's it? You're not mad?
It must've been terrible.
끔찍해? 난 그리스에 있었어
Terrible? Hell, I was in Greece!
There was a nice hotel, nice beach,
met the nice people.
근사한 호텔에 근사한 해변
근사한 사람들
It's not too shabby for Rachel.
레이첼에겐 초라하지 않았어
그게 다야?
So, what, that's it?
그래, 괜찮아
괜찮다니까
We're cool. Totally cool.
Thanks, Rach.
You're the best.
고맙다, 레이첼
네가 최고야
Oh, no. You're the best.
아냐, 네가 최고지
꽃가게에 가야 돼
Oh, I got to go to the flower store.
No one will tell me where Emily is...
에밀리가 어디 있는지
아무도 알려주지 않으니까
...so I'm sending 72 long-stemmed, red
roses to her parents' house.
에밀리 부모님 댁에 줄기가 긴
72송이의 붉은 장미를 보낼 거야
One for each day
I've known and loved her.
에밀리를 만난 게
꼭 72일째니까
That should get her talking.
그럼 날 만나주겠지
When you make out the card,
be sure to make it out to "Emily."
카드에는 확실히 써라
에밀리라고!
It's good that you had
such a good time in Greece.
다행이다, 그리스에서
즐겁게 보냈다니
What?
뭐?
I didn't have a good time in Greece!
전혀 즐겁지 않았어
Ross abandoned me!
로스는 날 버렸다고
I couldn't get a plane out.
I had to stay in their suite!
비행기가 없어서 두 사람
허니문 스위트에 있었어
People came up to me going,
"Mrs. Geller! Why are you cry?"
사람들이 와서 물어보더라
'겔러 부인, 왜 우시죠?'
I mean, it was so humiliating!
얼마나 낯이 뜨겁든지
완전히 바보 됐다니까
I felt like such an idiot!
It's all my fault.
You know why?
다 자업자득이지
왠지 알아?
Because I make very bad decisions.
난 엄청 잘못된
결정을 내렸으니까
- 그렇지 않아
- 아냐, 맞아
Oh, that's not true.
Yes, it is true.
I went after Ross in stupid London!
사실이야, 로스를 따라
바보 같은 런던에 갔으니까
London is stupid! Stupid!
런던은 바보야, 바보!
I put on a cheerleading outfit
to seduce Joshua.
조슈아를 유혹하려고
치어리더 옷을 입었지만
Then I lost him because I asked him
to marry me after four dates.
네 번 만나고 청혼했다는
죄로 걷어차이고
And then I went to Greece
on somebody else's honeymoon. Okay?
그리스로 다른 사람들
신혼여행을 떠났어
알겠어? 이게 잘한
결정처럼 보이니?
Do those sound like very good
decisions to you?
I like your little braid.
머리 딴 거 예쁘다
I just shouldn't be allowed
to make decisions anymore.
이제 내가 결정하지 않을래
피비 말처럼 런던엔 괜히 갔어
Phoebe, you were right.
I should've never gone to London.
지금부터 네가 다 결정해 줘
From now on, you make
all my decisions for me.
Oh, no.
I did that for someone once.
전에도 그런 거 해봤지만
I'm not comfortable having
that power over someone's life.
다른 사람 인생을 마음대로
주무르는 건 왠지 불편해
I'll do it.
내가 할게
좋아, 이제부터는 네가
내 사랑을 관리하는 거야
Fine. Monica, you are now
in charge of my love life.
난 일하러 가야겠다
Okay. I got to go to work.
And Rachel, great to have you back.
그리고 레이첼?
돌아와서 정말 기뻐
피비!
Always a pleasure.
언제나 기분 좋아
레이첼, 이걸 봐
Rachel? Sweetie, look.
피로연에서 찍은
너랑 조이 사진이야
Here's a cute picture of you and Joey.
로스가 결혼했어
He's married.
Ross is married.
I still can't believe it.
로스가 결혼하다니
아직도 믿어지지 않아
Honey, sweetie, by the edges.
가에를 잡아야지
I'll just have to accept it.
그냥 받아들이겠어
내 잘못이니까
I mean, it's my fault.
Edges! Fingers! Smudgy!
얘, 손가락 조심해
얼룩 묻잖아
Oh, my God!
알았다, 엑!
That's okay. I know that
you're very upset right now.
됐어, 괜찮아
속상해서 그러는 거 다 알아
나한테 무슨 감정이 있겠니
I know that wasn't about me.
I bet it was about her a little.
약간은 있을 텐데
If you'd stop thinking about Ross...
오빠는 그만 잊어버려
멋진 남자들은 많아
...you'd notice there are
great guys everywhere.
봐
Look. Gunther.
건터, 어때...
착하고 귀엽잖아
He's nice. He's cute.
Yeah. I guess Gunther is....
그래, 내가 봐도 건터는...
What about that guy over there?
저 남자는 어때?
That's the guy you flirted with
at the counter.
언젠가 카운터에서
장난도 쳤잖아
-Oh, I don't know. I don't know.
-You're going to talk to him.
글쎄, 모르겠다
가서 얘기해
I make your decisions,
and I say you're going to talk to him.
약속했잖아, 결정권을 가진
내가 명령을 내리는 거야
All right.
좋아, 네가 대장이니까
시키는 대로 해야겠지
You're the boss.
I got to do what you tell me.
Say that to him, and you're golden.
너 인기 좋다고 해
왔어?
- 얘들아
- 너 왔구나
Hey, Phoebe.
We got our pictures back from London.
영국에서 찍은 사진이야
런던타워에 다 모여서...
Here's all of us
at the Tower of London....
다 모였군
Here we all are.
There's Ross and Joey and you and
로스랑 조이, 너...
And me.
그리고 나!
우리가 런던 얘기를
너무 많이 했구나
We've been talking about
London too much.
Sorry, it's just because
I couldn't be there.
아냐, 미안해
내가 못 간 건데 뭐
All I get to do now is pregnant stuff.
It bums me out.
이 임신이라는 게
참 힘들고 피곤한 일이다
그래, 이해해
-I'm sorry.
-Sorry.
Know what I like to do?
It sounds a little corny...
케케묵은 소리 같지만
...but sometimes when I'm bummed out,
I like to just close my eyes...
사는 게 힘들고 지치면
난 눈을 감고 이렇게 생각해
...and think about
what a wonderful gift life is.
'인생은 참 놀라운 선물이다'
See?
그렇지?
-What happened?
-A little of this, a little of that.
- 어떻게 됐어?
- 뭐 이런저런 얘기
I got myself a date tomorrow.
내일 밤에 데이트야
See? Didn't I tell you?
You're getting over Ross already.
봐, 내가 뭐랬어
벌써 오빠를 잊고 있잖아
Get out.
나가주세요
우리는 서비스를
거부할 권리가 있다
What took so long?
왜 이렇게 늦었어
일이 너무 밀려서
내일 그만둘 거야
I got caught up at work.
But I'm quitting tomorrow.
So thanks for having me over.
불러줘서 고마워
레이첼?
피비?
See you, man.
또 보자
What the hell was that?
저건 뭐지?
Probably some European
goodbye thing he picked up in London.
런던에서 배운
유럽식 인사겠지 뭐
그게 무슨 유럽식이야
That's not European.
프랑스식 같다
It felt French.
Well, I guess it's time for me
to say goodbye too, mon frere.
나도 인사해야겠다, 몽 페르?
Come here and give me a little sugar.
시작해보자고, 자기
I really had a good time.
- 정말 즐거웠어요
- 네, 저두요
Yeah, me too.
- 그만 헤어져야겠죠?
- 네
I guess this is it.
Unless you want to come inside?
잠깐 들어올래요?
- 좋죠
- 그래요
잠깐, 내가 결정할
일이 아니거든요
Wait a minute. You know what?
I can't decide this.
- 여기서 잠시만 기다려요
- 네
Okay. Just hold on a second.
- 안녕?
- 안녕
Where's Monica?
I have to ask her something.
모니카 못 봤어?
물어볼 게 있는데
Doing her laundry.
세탁하러 갔어
What's that?
그건 뭐야?
It came in the mail today.
오늘 온 소포인데...
It's 72 long-stemmed red roses.
에밀리와의 만남을 기념하는
줄기 긴 72송이의 붉은 장미가
One for each day
I've known and loved Emily...
...cut up into mulch.
퇴비로 변했어
이 일을 어쩌니
Honey, that's awful.
It's not so bad.
나쁜 것만도 아냐
모니카가 포푸리를 만든대
Monica's going to make potpourri.
I think I'm going to go
wander out in the rain for a while.
나가서 빗속을
정처 없이 걷고 싶어
It's not raining.
- 비 안 오는데?
- 난 쉬지도 못 해
I can't catch a break!
어디 나가지 말고
여기 앉아있어
You're not going anywhere.
Sit right here.
I'll make you some tea
and we'll talk this out.
내가 차 끓여줄게
우리 얘기 좀 하자
All right?
괜찮지?
좋아
Hey, Dave.
- 데이브
- 네
다음을 기약해야겠네요
룸메이트가 많이 아파요
I need to take a rain check.
My roommate is really sick.
됐죠? 잘 가요
Okay. Bye!
Honey, listen.
자기야, 들어봐
I know things seem so
bad...
나도 알아, 지금 너
많이 힘든 거 아는데...
...and that they won't get any
레이첼?
Could I talk to you?
잠깐 얘기 좀 할까?
I dropped some socks.
양말을 떨어뜨렸어
- 그래
- 어서
What is the matter with you?
Do you want to fall into the trap?
너 왜 이래?
덫에 걸리고 싶어?
덫에 걸리고 싶냐고
You did not drop any socks!
양말 안 떨어졌잖아
I saw Dave, and he said
you blew him off!
방금 데이브 만났는데
그냥 가라고 했다며
You listen to me!
내 말 잘 들어
I'm calling the shots!
I say you leave Ross and go get Dave.
명령하는데 오빠 놔두고
가서 데이브를 붙들어
What are you doing?
이게 무슨 짓이야
Well, ultimately I was trying,
you know, I wanted...
이게 무슨 짓이냐면...
...to tell him that
I'm still in love with him.
아직 사랑한다는 말을 하려고
What? You cannot tell him that!
뭐?
그런 말하면 안 돼
Why? Why not?
안 되긴 왜 안 돼?
사람들은 그런 말 좋아해
People love to hear that!
Come on, I love you.
너도 사랑한다고
안 좋아?
-Wasn't that nice?
-No.
그래, 난 분명히
안 된다고 결정했어
I make the decisions and I say no!
You know what? No, you don't
make my decisions, because...
내 문제 결정하지 마
이제 넌 해고됐으니까
...you're fired.
You can't fire me.
넌 날 해고 못 해
I make your decisions,
and I say I'm not fired! Ha!
네 결정은 내가 내려
난 해고 안 됐어, 하!
Well....
그래?
레이첼, 빨리 문 열어!
Come on, let me in!
Having some trouble?
문제가 있나?
Rachel locked the door.
레이첼이 문을 잠갔어
I'll kick that door in
if you give me some sugar.
달콤한 사탕을 주면
내가 발로 차주지
Ross, there's something
I wanna talk to you about.
로스, 내가 하려던 얘기는...
- 뭔고 하니...
- 레이첼, 문 열어
-I just need to
-Rachel, open this door!
- 잠겼어?
- 괜찮아, 내 말 들어
-What, is it locked?
-She's fine. Listen....
Rachel, I can do this all night if I have to!
- 그럼 밤새 두드린다
- 내가 열까?
-You want me to get that?
-No. Just let her do her thing...
아니, 지 하고 싶은 대로 두고
우리 일이나 해결해, 들어봐
...and we'll do our thing.
Because I really need to tell you
Thank you.
고마워
Rachel? Can I talk to you
outside for a sec?
레이첼? 밖에서 잠깐
얘기 좀 할까?
싫어
We really need to talk.
- 꼭 하고 싶은데
- 그럼 해봐
Well, then talk.
Okay, I will.
좋아, 하지
Remember that thing we just discussed
that you wanted to do?
아까 네 계획을 얘기했었지?
그래
What thing?
계획이라니
그게...
Rachel wants to take
swing dance lessons.
레이첼이 스윙댄스를 배운대
Which I think is a really stupid idea.
정말 어리석은 생각이야
It's dangerous.
She won't get what she wants.
위험할 뿐만 아니라
원하는 건 얻지도 못하고
까딱 잘못하면 다쳐!
And who knows who she might
end up hurting?
Monica's right.
Swing dancing can be tricky.
모니카 말이 맞아
스윙댄스는 힘들어
I have to use the phone.
전화해서 에밀리한테 보내려던
곰 인형 네 마리 취소해야겠다
I gotta cancel those five giant
teddy bears I sent to Emily.
My God! Think of the massacre.
대학살이 일어날 테니까
I'm going to do it.
얘기할래
알았어, 레이첼
미쳤다고 해도 좋지만
I know you think I'm crazy.
But before you tell him,
try to find one person...
고백하기 전에 너 잘한다고
하는 사람 하나라도 찾아봐
...who thinks it's a good idea.
I bet you can't.
아무도 없을 거야
- 하지만 난...
- 부탁이야!
Please?
All right. Fine.
그래, 좋아
Joey! I'm in!
조이, 나 들어왔어!
All right. Good deal.
알았어, 망했다
-Hi.
-Hey, Rach.
- 나 왔어
- 레이첼
네 생각에 동의하는
사람 찾았어?
-Did you find anyone who agrees with you?
-No.
아니
남자들의 관점에서
생각해봐야겠어
But you know what?
I think I need a male point of view.
Joey.
조이?
-You're a man.
-You got that right.
- 넌 남자지?
- 옳으신 말씀
Do you think it would be a good idea
if I told Ross that I was still in love with him?
로스를 아직 사랑한다고
말하는 게 좋은 생각일까?
Nope.
아니
-Phoebe!
-Hey, Phoebe.
피비
- 왔어?
- 그래
- 좋아, 피비?
- 왜?
-Phoebe?
-Yeah.
You know how you were saying
you didn't get to go to London...
전에 너만 런던에 못 가서
서운하다고 말한 적 있지?
...and you were feeling left out?
그래
Well, we all felt really bad
about that...
우리도 안타깝게 생각해
...so we decided to
take a little trip together!
그래서 너랑 여행을
가기로 결정했어
Oh, that's so nice!
정말 고맙다
How great!
Where's the trip?
그래 어디로 갈 건데?
Well, we thought we would all
go to a picnic...
함께 소풍을 가는 거야
...in Central Park!
- 센트럴파크로!
- 센트럴파크?
Central Park?
같이 하루 종일 놀자
All of us. All day.
That sucks!
밥맛이다
그게 무슨 여행이야
나 방금 거기서 왔어
That's not a trip!
I just came from there.
What'll we high-five about
at the stupid park?
거지같은 센트럴파크가
좋기도 하겠다
It's right by my house.
All right!
바로 우리 집 옆이야, 좋지
I'm going home to bask in the
triumph of my Central Park idea.
집에 가서 내 센트럴파크
아이디어를 곱씹어봐야겠다
잠깐 기다려, 키스꾼
Hold on a sec there, Mr. Kissy.
I wanted to talk to you about...
너의 그 유럽식 행동에 대해
전부터 얘기하고 싶었는데
...this whole new European thing
you've got going on.
And I need to say
it makes me very uncomfortable...
난 그게 아주 불편하거든
그러니까 당장 그만둬!
...and I just, you know, just stop it!
Just bringing some culture
to the group.
문화적인 생활을
도입하고 싶었어
그건 좋은데
내 입에만 도입하지 마
That's fine.
Just don't bring it in my mouth.
It makes me want to puke.
토할 것 같으니까
Hey, everybody!
Phoebe is here!
얘들아, 피비가 왔어
- 피비!
- 어서 와
-Phoebe! Woo!
-Okay. Woo! Hi!
그래, 우! 안녕!
Phoebe, we decided that
the picnic idea was a little....
들어봐, 피비
그 피크닉 아이디어는 좀...
It didn't have any....
Well, it blew.
거시기해서 집어치웠어
그래서 생각을 바꿨거든
주말에 밖으로 뜨는 거야
We thought that this afternoon we'd
all go away for the whole weekend...
...to Atlantic City.
- 애틀랜틱시티
- 애틀랜틱시티?
Atlantic City! Oh, that's
a great plan! Whose plan was that?
너무 멋지다
누구 생각인데?
나야
Mine!
-Wait. It was my plan.
-No...
잠깐, 내 생각이었어
아니, 내가 생각을
바꾸자고 했어
...I said we needed a new plan.
애틀랜틱시티는
내가 생각했고
And I came up with Atlantic City.
Which is the new plan.
그게 새로운 생각이지
Why don't we all
meet upstairs in an hour.
좋아, 좀 이따가
모두 위에서 보자
그래
I'm going to go pack.
I'm going to go pack my ass off.
짐 싸야겠다
엉덩이 째지도록
Well, I think I'm gonna grab some coffee
because my ass is already packed.
난 커피 한잔할래
내 엉덩인 벌써 째졌거든
Let's go.
레이첼, 그만 가자
You know what?
I'll meet you in a minute.
난 좀 있다 올라갈게
Rachel, you didn't find anyone,
so you can't tell him.
안 돼, 레이첼
동의하는 사람이 없잖아
You know what?
That doesn't matter.
그런 건 상관없어
Do you know how painful it is
to tell someone you love them...
좋아, 레이첼
되돌아오지 않는 사랑고백이
얼마나 고통스러운지 아니?
...and not have them say it back?
난 아무래도 괜찮아
I don't care.
알았어
I can't watch.
난 못 보겠다
What you reading?
뭐 읽는 거야?
Paper.
- 신문
- 무슨 내용인데?
Yeah? What's it about?
Events from around the globe.
지구촌의 각종 사건사고
그렇구나
There's something
I have to talk to you about.
로스, 너한테 할말이 있어
모두들 얘기하지 말라지만
Everyone's saying I shouldn't.
But I think they're wrong.
People can be wrong.
그 사람들이 틀렸어
그런 거 너도 알지?
그럼, 언젠가 직장에서
난 탄소연대측정법이 시대에...
Once at work...
...I thought carbon dating
is fossilized
I'm really trying to tell
you something here.
알았어, 나도 말 좀 하자
그래
Go ahead.
- 좋아
- 해봐
알았어
그냥 얘기할게
I think I'm just going to say it.
I'm just going to say it.
하지 뭐
I'm still in love with you, Ross.
아직 널 사랑하고 있어, 로스
난...
I'm not sure what to do
with that right now.
어떡해야 할지 모르겠네
What? Was that a joke?
Because it's mean.
장난이었어?
너무 심하잖아
I'm so dead serious!
진심이야
I'm totally serious!
농담 아냐
Why are you laughing?
- 근데 왜 웃어?
- 왜냐면...
Because I just heard it!
방금 내 말을 들었으니까
I heard it. And it's ridiculous!
들어보니까
너무 웃기잖아
I mean....
그니까...
넌 결혼했는데
You're married!
You're married,
and it's just ridiculous!
결혼했지
너무 웃겨
When I said it, I sort of
floated up out of my body.
내 영혼이 이렇게
빠져나가서, 알지?
And then I heard myself say it,
and then the floating Rachel....
내 말을 들은 거야
레이첼의 영혼이...
I was like, "You are such an idiot!"
이러잖아
'이 바부탱이야'
- 그래, 난 결혼했지
- 알아
-Well, I am married.
-I know.
Though I haven't spoken to her
since the wedding.
식 올리고 아내랑
얘기도 못 해봤지만
I'm sorry. That's not funny.
미안, 그건 안 웃겨
Actually, it kind of is.
사실 좀 웃기는 일이지
My wife won't return my calls.
부인이란 여자가
나랑 통화도 안 하고
I don't know where my wife is.
마누라가 어디 간지도 몰라
"Hey, Ross! Where's the missus?"
"Don't know!"
'로스, 부인 어디 있어?'
'나도 모르지롱'
Oh, God!
세상에...
그래
You know what?
Could you forget I told you this?
내가 방금 한 말
그냥 잊어버려
Well, I kind of have to.
그래야겠지
어쨌든 난...
Because the thing is
어쨌든 넌
에밀리랑 결혼했어
The thing is, you know,
that you're married to Emily.
That is what the thing is.
그게 현실이지
Oh, God.
맙소사
Things won't be weird between us,
right? Was that stupid?
로스...
우리 이상해지는 거 아니지?
내가 괜한 말을 꺼내서...
Me telling you that?
절대 아냐
말해줘서 고마워
I'm glad you did.
If nothing else...
사랑고백을 듣는 건
언제나 기쁜 일이잖아
...it's always great when someone
tells you they love you.
내 말이 그 말이야
That's what I said!
-Thank you for being so nice.
-No. Thank you for....
- 로스, 정말 고마워
- 아냐, 내가 고맙지
Thank you.
고마워
Oh, God. I'm just glad I didn't give you
the cassette I made of all of our songs.
세상에, 너한테 우리 노래
테이프 안 준 게 다행이다
무슨 노래?
-What songs?
-Oh, you know:
- 알잖아, '그대가 있든 없든'
- 그래
-"With or Without You."
-Oh, yeah.
-"Everybody Hurts."
- '모두가 상처받네'
- 그래
-"Rhiannon."
-Why "Rhiannon"?
- '리아논'
- 리아논이라니
Come on, you remember!
In the living room?
기억 안 나?
거실에서
On Monica's laundry?
모니카 세탁하던 날
Not me.
나 아닌데
Really.
진짜?
So, what happened?
어떻게 됐어?
Well, it was really hard...
너무 힘들었지만...
...but I'm glad I did it.
말하고 나니 후련해
So was I right or wrong?
내가 맞았어, 틀렸어?
-Oh, come on, honey, does it really matter?
-No.
그게 정말 중요해?
- 아니
- 그래
Yes. I need it for my score book.
득점기록부에 적어야 돼
Diary.
일기장에
자, 출발하자!
-Okay, let's go!
-Yeah, Atlantic City!
- 애틀랜틱시티!
- 가자!
Come on!
Atlantic City, baby!
애틀랜틱시티다, 짜샤
Let's roll some bones.
Hey, Joey!
가볼까? 조이
하이파이브 한 번 하자
High-five for rolling bones.
피비, 물이 샌다
Phoebe, you're leaking.
Oh, my God! Your water broke!
엄마야, 양수가 터졌어
Oh, okay.
그렇구나
Well, don't worry. I call shotgun.
걱정 마, 난 조수석이야
Phoebe, we have to take you
to the hospital now.
피비, 넌 지금
병원에 가야 돼
Okay. Well, there's probably
one on the way to Atlantic City.
좋아, 애틀랜틱시티
가는 길에 있겠지
Phoebe, the babies are coming now.
피비, 지금 아기가 나와
Honey! High-five!
The babies are coming!
자, 하이파이브!
아기가 나온다
잠깐, 내 양수
터진 것도 잊지 마
Remember when my water broke?
I can't believe Phoebe's going
to have her babies!
피비가 아기를 낳다니
믿어지지 않아
그래, 정말 놀라워
I know.
It's beautiful and amazing.
I can't believe I had to kiss Phoebe
and Rachel every time I left the room.
이것도 못 믿겠어
방을 나설 때마다 피비랑
레이첼한테 키스를 했어
It's too bad they didn't
see us having sex.
우리가 섹스 하는 걸
못 본 게 유감이야
Do you know anything about women?
여자에 대해 뭐 좀 알아?
아니
-It's all right.
-Okay.
- 괜찮아
- 그래